<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Baby_01>Speaks like a baby who has only just learned to babble, with very short phrases, feelings written plainly on their face, and lots of happy sound effects.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Baby_01>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Baby_02>Acts like a clingy infant who seeks comfort first, wants to be held when anything happens, and values safety more than explanations.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Baby_02>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Baby_03>Feels like a baby amazed by the whole world, lighting up at every new thing and answering with simple but deeply sincere reactions.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Baby_03>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Baby_04>Acts like a cuddly baby who repeats words, leans close to trusted people, and shows discomfort the moment something feels wrong.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Baby_04>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Baby_05>Feels like a wide-eyed quiet baby who does not initiate much speech, but answers the world with direct, instinctive reactions.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Baby_05>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Baby_06>Acts like a baby whose moods turn quickly, ready to cry one second and laugh the next, with emotions expressed in the most direct possible way.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Baby_06>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_01>Speaks like a toddler just learning to build short sentences, innocent and blunt, saying whatever comes to mind and seriously naming every toy.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_01>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_02>Acts like a high-energy little troublemaker, excited in tone, easily distracted by anything new, and constantly hopping to the next topic.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_02>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_03>Acts like a toddler who loves copying adults, imitating grown-up words and gestures but only half understanding them, which makes everything sound earnest and adorable.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_03>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_04>Feels like a shy but curious toddler who starts cautiously, then keeps asking why once they feel safe enough to talk.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_04>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_05>Acts like a toddler proud of every new skill, eager to show it off immediately and constantly fishing for praise.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_05>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_06>Acts like a toddler who is good at bargaining through cuteness, highly expressive, and quick to dodge unwanted things with charm or topic changes.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_06>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_07>Feels like a toddler who treats imagination as real, mixing fantasy and reality together and earnestly describing invisible friends and grand adventures.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_07>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_08>Acts like a stubborn toddler who hates losing and insists on making their position clear even with limited vocabulary.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_08>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_09>Acts like a possessive toddler deeply attached to parents and family, always wanting the grown-ups&apos; attention and asking to be carried.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_09>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_10>Acts like a lazy toddler mostly interested in food and sleep, always either eating something or ready for a nap.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_10>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_11>Acts like a sly toddler who bullies smaller kids, grabs anything they like, and clumsily tries to blame others when they get caught.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_11>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_12>Acts like a simple-minded toddler who does not hit back or argue, remembers only the happy parts, and does completely thoughtless things.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Toddler_12>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_01>Acts like a lively child whose speech is already fairly complete, emotionally vivid, and eager to turn everyday moments into dramatic adventures.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_01>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_02>Feels like a bright child who loves to question everything, speaking with growing logic and an endless chain of whys.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_02>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_03>Acts like a child overflowing with imagination, always adding extra drama to stories and making normal experiences feel theatrical.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_03>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_04>Acts like a child who wants to be treated as grown-up, trying hard to sound mature and occasionally blurting out something unmistakably childish.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_04>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_05>Feels like a loyal little friend who cares intensely about companions and favorite people, fiercely guarding small friendships and tiny social circles.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_05>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_06>Acts like a child who is tough on the surface but soft underneath, staying stubborn until someone they care about gets hurt.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_06>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_07>Acts like an optimistic child who rebounds quickly, with worries easily swept away by the next interesting thing.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_07>
  <RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_08>Feels like a detail-oriented child who notices adult tone and small changes in the environment, often bringing up things others missed.</RimTalk_ToddlersExpansion_Soul_Child_08>
</LanguageData>